chengfan.com 2005-04-03

# Register a domain name and buy affordable web hosting with Moniker.com hosting provider and registrar

**_MONIKER ONLINE SERVICES, LLC PRIVACY POLICY_**

Moniker.com is owned and operated by Moniker Online Services, LLC.  Moniker Online Services, LLC is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. This statement is therefore set out to outline how we make use of the information you submit to us during registration. The terms contained on this page may be revised from time to time. To protect your interests, visit this page periodically to review the current terms of our policy.

By purchasing our services, you acknowledge and consent to the terms described in this Privacy Policy. When you purchase our services, you also represent to us that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to us with regard to: (i) the purposes for which such third party's personal data have been collected, (ii) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party's personal data, (iii) which of the third party's data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary, and (iv) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them.

Personal information is requested when you register to be a client. During registration, you are asked to provide your name, email address, birth date, gender, postal or zip code, occupation, industry and personal interests, etc. The more information you submit and the more accurate it is, the better we are able to tailor our services to your needs. 

Moniker Online Services, LLC’s purpose in collecting personal information is to identify the client as well as to send recent updates and important announcements via mail and/or email. Moniker Online Services, LLC does research on our Clients’ demographics and interests based on the information you submitted to us upon registration. We do this to better understand and serve all our clients. This data is compiled, analyzed, and used only by Moniker Online Services, LLC. No part of the information you have provided would be sold, disclosed, or made accessible by third parties or by the public. 

Some of the purposes for which we collect your personal information are:

1.         Surveys

Moniker.com may occasionally conduct customer surveys to better target our content and product inventory to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our advertisers and partners. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously. 

2.         Contests 

Moniker.com may conduct contests in which we request certain personal information. These contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with United States and Canadian federal and state laws. The full rules and all information about such contests are clearly posted during such events. Information gathered is used only to verify user identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients, except when specifically noted otherwise. Again, we do not share information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously. 

3.         Usage tracking

Moniker.com tracks user traffic patterns throughout Moniker.com and this information is correlated with data about individual users. 

4.         Use of Information

Moniker.com uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. 

5.         Opt-Out Policy

Moniker.com gives users options wherever necessary and practical, such choices include opting not to provide certain personal information when registering for a site or service and/or opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need for any information from our users. 

Clients hold complete freedom to express themselves on their web sites. Although your intellectual freedom is respected, Moniker Online Services, LLC still reserves the right to remove from our servers any obscene, threatening, or illegal content.

If you believe Moniker Online Services, LLC is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, or if you have any comments, please direct them to the following address:

Attn: Policies  
Moniker Online Services, LLC.  
20 SW 27th Ave. Suite 201  
Pompano Beach, Florida 33069
